in this screencast we'll see how to work
在此截屏视频中，我们将了解如何工作
with maven projects firstly let's create
首先与Maven项目一起创建
a brand new maven project we select
我们选择一个全新的Maven项目
maven from the options on the left and
从左侧的选项行家
then we can choose the JDK for the
那么我们可以为
project here we'll stick with the latest
项目在这里，我们将坚持最新
version of Java 8 and we can optionally
Java 8版本，我们可以选择
choose a maven archetype to use to
选择要使用的Maven原型
create the project we're going to create
创建我们将要创建的项目
a simple project so you won't select an
一个简单的项目，因此您不会选择
archetype for maven projects we need to
我们需要的Maven项目原型
declare a group ID and the artifact idea
声明组ID和工件想法
of the application itself if we want we
我们想要的应用程序本身
can call the project something different
可以给项目打电话不同的东西
to the artifacts ID but for this example
到工件ID，但在此示例中
we'll keep defaults IntelliJ IDEA will
我们将保留默认值IntelliJ IDEA将
generate the maven pom to XML view which
生成Maven pom到XML视图
you can see here you can choose whether
你可以在这里看到你可以选择是否
to import any changes from the pom file
从pom文件导入任何更改
manually after you make them or choose
制作或选择后手动
to have IntelliJ IDEA automatically
自动具有IntelliJ IDEA
import any changes as soon as they're
导入任何更改
made because this is a small project and
因为这是一个小项目，
importing changes is probably not going
导入更改可能不会
to take too long for this example we'll
这个例子花的时间太长了
choose to enable auto import as well as
选择启用自动导入以及
creating the basic pom to XML IntelliJ
创建XML IntelliJ的基本pom
IDEA has also created the default
IDEA还创建了默认
directory structure for amazing projects
出色项目的目录结构
with the source and test folders defined
定义了源文件夹和测试文件夹
when we open the maven project window we
当我们打开Maven项目窗口时，
can see the standard maven lifecycle
可以看到标准的Maven生命周期
phases as well as the goals defined by
阶段以及目标定义
various maven plugins we can easily add
我们可以轻松添加各种Maven插件
new dependencies by generate on the code
通过在代码上生成新的依赖项
menu or using command n on the Mac or
菜单或在Mac上使用命令n或
often insert on Windows and Linux as
通常在Windows和Linux上以
you'd expect from IntelliJ IDEA you get
您期望从IntelliJ IDEA获得
code completion inside the dependency
依赖内的代码完成
template to help you find the dependency
模板，以帮助您找到依赖关系
you're looking for you can see all your
您正在寻找，您可以看到所有
declared dependencies in the maven
在Maven中声明依赖
window nested under those we've declared
嵌套在我们声明的窗口之下
you can see the dependencies they
你可以看到他们的依赖
themselves rely on when you look in the
当你看着
project window you can see all the maven
您可以在项目窗口中看到所有的专家
dependencies regardless of whether
依赖关系，无论是否
they're declared by your project or
它们是由您的项目声明的，或者
pulled in as a transitive dependency
作为传递依赖引入
while it's possible you may want to
虽然有可能您可能想要
create your own maven project as we have
创建我们自己的Maven项目
done here it's much more likely you'll
在这里完成，您很有可能会
import an existing one this is very
导入现有的这是非常
straightforward
直截了当
select import project and navigate the
选择导入项目并浏览
location of the code you can select the
您可以选择代码的位置
root of the project and IntelliJ IDEA
项目和IntelliJ IDEA的根
will figure out how to import it but if
会弄清楚如何导入它，但是如果
you specifically know this is amazing
你特别知道这很棒
project and you want to use this model
项目，您想使用此模型
for your project structure its simplest
对于您的项目结构，最简单
to select the top-level pom file and the
选择顶级pom文件和
IDE will know you mean to import a maven
IDE会知道您要导入Maven
project generally we'll want to keep the
项目，我们通常要保持
default settings but here I would like
默认设置，但在这里我想
to make sure that any sub projects are
确保任何子项目
located and set up correctly I can
找到并正确设置我可以
select to automatically Rhian fort the
选择自动将Rhian Fort
project if we make any changes to the
如果我们对项目进行任何更改
pond or XML file in this case I don't
在这种情况下，池或XML文件不会
want to at this time because for most
想要在这个时候，因为对于大多数
non-trivial projects is can take some
非平凡的项目可能需要一些时间
time and I prefer to have control over
时间，我更喜欢控制
when I apply the changes for everything
当我将更改应用于所有内容时
else
其他
we'll keep the defaults the next screen
我们将在下一个屏幕上保留默认设置
will show is all the maven projects
将显示所有Maven项目
IntelliJ IDEA has found to import in
IntelliJ IDEA已发现要导入
this case it's just one I'm going to
这只是我要去的一个案例
keep the default JDK and default project
保留默认的JDK和默认项目
name and pass IntelliJ IDEA will use the
名称并通过IntelliJ IDEA将使用
maven definition to figure out the
Maven的定义来找出
structure of the application and of
应用程序的结构和
course download all the required
课程下载所有必需的
dependencies and add them to the project
依赖项并将它们添加到项目中
you can use command e or control e to
您可以使用命令e或控制e来
navigate to the maven window and here we
导航到Maven窗口，在这里我们
can see the dependencies of this project
可以看到这个项目的依赖
as before this window lists the goals
和之前一样，此窗口列出了目标
and lifecycle phases we can run any of
和生命周期阶段，我们可以运行
these by double clicking on them and we
通过双击它们，我们
can see the familiar results of running
可以看到跑步的熟悉结果
a maven phase in the run window
运行窗口中的Maven阶段
including dependencies being downloaded
包括正在下载的依赖项
and tests being run let's skip watching
和正在运行的测试让我们跳过观看
the full thing and see the results our
完整的东西，看看结果我们
build was successful and we can see
构建成功，我们可以看到
maven has created a target directory
maven已经创建了一个目标目录
with all the generated code and the
与所有生成的代码和
other output of course we can run the
其他输出当然我们可以运行
project's tests via maven which is
通过Maven进行项目测试
particularly useful if there's a complex
如果有复杂的情况特别有用
setup phase in maven to get the tests
在Maven中进行设置阶段以获取测试
running but we can also simply run all
运行，但我们也可以简单地运行所有
tests or a subset of them from IntelliJ
测试或IntelliJ中的一部分
IDEA as usual
像往常一样的想法
editing the Palm D'Or XML file is easy
编辑Palm D'Or XML文件很容易
and of course you get full code
当然你会得到完整的代码
completion if you're working with maze
如果正在使用迷宫，则完成
and profiles IntelliJ IDEA makes this
和配置文件IntelliJ IDEA做到了
simple you can choose to enable or
简单，您可以选择启用或
disable one or more profiles when you're
停用时，禁用一个或多个配置文件
running any of the maven goals or phases
运行任何行家目标或阶段
there are a number of things you can do
您可以做很多事情
with your projects in the Maven window
在Maven窗口中处理项目
be sure to take a look at all the icons
一定要看看所有的图标
to see what they can do
看看他们能做什么
everything we've looked at so far has
到目前为止，我们所看到的一切
been in the free community edition of
曾在的免费社区版中
IntelliJ IDEA the full ultimate version
IntelliJ IDEA完整版
has some extra features one which may be
有一些额外的功能可能是
particularly useful in understanding
在理解方面特别有用
your maven project Aseema dependencies
您的Maven项目Aseema依赖项
as a diagram this can give you an idea
作为一个图，这可以给你一个想法
of which dependencies are directly
直接依赖
imported by your application and which
由您的应用程序导入以及
are transitive you can also see test
具有传递性，您还可以查看测试
dependencies in green and any unresolved
绿色的依赖项以及任何未解决的依赖项
ones will be in red you can change the
那些会变成红色，您可以更改
visibility of a dependency or exclude it
依赖项的可见性或将其排除
via the diagram you can also filter
通过图表，您还可以过滤
which ones to show if the diagram is too
如果图表也显示哪些
big to see easily in this video we've
很容易在这个视频中看到
covered the basics of working with maven
涵盖了使用Maven的基础知识
and IntelliJ IDEA take a look at the
和IntelliJ IDEA一起看看
documentation for more details or check
文档以获取更多详细信息或查看
out the YouTube channel for more video
在YouTube频道中观看更多视频
tutorials thanks for watching
教程谢谢收看